<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>American Statistical Association-Twin Cities Chapter</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on American Statistical Association-Twin Cities Chapter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>UPCOMING EVENT Spring 2019: Reproducible Science - April</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/04/17/spring2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/04/17/spring2019/</guid>
      <description>DATE AND TIME Mon, April 16, 2019
5:30 PM – 9:00 PM CDT
LOCATION Pizza Luce
119 N 4th St
Minneapolis, MN 55401
INVITED TALKS &amp;ldquo;Treatment Allocation Using a Multi-Armed Bandit Approach&amp;rdquo; Sakshi Arya In medical practice, different treatments are available for a certain disease and a doctor decides which treatment to use on a patient. Multi Armed Bandit with Covariates (MABC) is a reinforcement learning approach that learns from and adapts to present and past information to achieve maximum benefit for the patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPCOMING EVENT: Fall Member Meeting and Networking - October 9</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/09/03/fall2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/09/03/fall2018/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring 2018: Student Seminars and Networking Event</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/04/17/spring2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/04/17/spring2018/</guid>
      <description>DATE AND TIME Mon, April 16, 2018
5:30 PM – 9:00 PM CDT
LOCATION Pizza Luce
119 N 4th St
Minneapolis, MN 55401
INVITED TALKS &amp;ldquo;Treatment Allocation Using a Multi-Armed Bandit Approach&amp;rdquo; Sakshi Arya In medical practice, different treatments are available for a certain disease and a doctor decides which treatment to use on a patient. Multi Armed Bandit with Covariates (MABC) is a reinforcement learning approach that learns from and adapts to present and past information to achieve maximum benefit for the patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2017: Research Short Course and Seminars</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/10/09/fall2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/10/09/fall2017/</guid>
      <description>DATE AND TIME Mon, October 9, 2017
8:30 AM – 5:00 PM CDT
LOCATION University of St. Thomas (Downtown Minneapolis Campus)
1000 LaSalle Avenue
Opus Hall #201
Minneapolis, MN 55403
SHORT COURSE &amp;ldquo;Multi-State Survival Models&amp;rdquo; Presenter: Terry Therneau , Mayo Clinic &amp;ldquo;Time until event&amp;rdquo; is a recurring question in medical research: time until death (survival) and the impact of various covariates on that outcome is the traditional example, but the methods apply to any ongoing process: the time until recurrence of cancer, waiting time on the liver transplant list, the onset of comorbidities with aging, the time until return to work (economics) and industrial reliability are a few examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/blog/2015/07/23/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015/07/23/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our products? As am hastily invited settled at limited civilly fortune me. Really spring in extent an by. Judge but built gay party world. Of so am he remember although required. Bachelor unpacked be advanced at. Confined in declared marianne is vicinity.
Please feel free to contact us, our customer service center is working for you 24&amp;frasl;7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/</guid>
      <description> Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Membership</title>
      <link>/membership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/membership/</guid>
      <description>Join national ASA and our chapter Navigate to the ASA membership page. When given the option to select chapters, select the Twin Cities Chapter.
Join only our ASA chapter Use the form provided here  or email us  directly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>